[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Just fine, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Life good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Couldn't be better.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "Do you ever stop to actually look back and think, good god?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Well, at my age, you do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "What do you think when you think back to those days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "I love what happened because I had -- all my uncles and aunts and nieces and nephews, they were all good people, hard working people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What values did they instill in you, that community you had, family and friends?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "They just like -- well, besides great food.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "And you sing for your supper, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "That's what happened, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Is that when you got that excitement, that you thought this is for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "I remember very clearly saying, this is who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "You know you get to go and sing or paint or whatever it may be, but everything you do, you love doing, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "ENNETT: It's never a bother for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sony Columbia"]}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNPS", "NNP", "''", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "VB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Do any of the ones on this album match up in quality of voice to the greats like Sinatra or it is different these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, you know, I started with the \"Duets I.\" It was so successful that Sony Columbia said please do another one like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Is it as good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "They were all very professional, they were all prepared.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "She was so sweet to everybody, to every stage hand and everybody, thank you for being so nice to me and all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Especially in your great country Britain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "How long was that period for you when you were slightly feeling maybe it's over?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "I tell you, it was about six months.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Having had all this success, how did that period make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "I don't feel like ever retiring.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Rolands", "Woody Allen", "Lenny Bruce"]}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "When you see the younger stars these days or younger entertainer, they're not called necessarily stars, but when you see how much more available drugs now are even than they were in your day perhaps, does it concern you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "JJR", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "I learned -- Jack Rolands, Woody Allen's manager, he said that he managed Lenny Bruce years ago, who's a brilliant man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Do you feel fortunate that you were able to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "It was a blessing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Did you have friends, colleagues and so on who were not so fortunate, who just ended up being ruined by drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, that's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Because to me she was one of the best singer/songwriters to have emerged in a very, very long time, wasn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Mm-hmm, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Where were you, Tony, when you heard that she died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "I was at home.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tony"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "How did you hear about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "My son called me up and told me she just died.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Could you tell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Very sad, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "It is very sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "I mean, when people are huge entertainers, it brings with it particular pressures, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "At any given moment you can learn.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Squeaky clean as imagine you must be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "No, I -- actually --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "You drink -- do you drink at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I have a glass of wine at night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Presumably the cocaine days are behind you now, Tony?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Completely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "How important is self-discipline for a singer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "It's something you can't teach.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "And it's dangerous, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "What's happening to me right now is I have a new album, I'm not just plugging this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "How much -- how much of your ability to be successful for so long do you think is down to having strong people like your mother in your early life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "It meant everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Well, that was your theme tune, isn't it, really, \"I Left My Heart in San Francisco\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "``", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "That's my signature song.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["San Francisco"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Do you ever get tired of singing it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "If you had five minutes to live, what song would you sing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "ENNETT: I'd sing the last line of that song.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "\"Your golden sun will shine for me.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Did you think then when Martin Luther King was assassinated, did you think in your lifetime, you would see a black president in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "I think it's the greatest accomplishment that the United States ever came up with.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Martin Luther King"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "What was driving you at the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "It's a dream of mine that someday the world will pick themselves up by their boot straps and better themselves, walk toward humanity, realize what a gift it is to be alive and to be on this planet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Was that -- was that how you felt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ":", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 347, "question": "But do you feel that war is ever justified?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "With all the collateral damage that comes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "It's a very difficult question, because I think we should have a society of highly educated, intelligent people that will think realistically about how to do things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Was that really the point you were making?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "IN", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What does it mean to you to be an American?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Well, America -- to be an American is you're ahead of everybody on the planet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "-- around the world, it would a very different world, right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 407, "question": "How did you go about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "You know, I started working with Tony -- my dad --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "-NONE-", "''", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Was that part of your thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "And at a time when rock 'n' roll people stopped taking chances, Tony never stopped.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "I mean, do you feel very protective towards your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, yes, but I don't have to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Do you look at young people today and say, I wish you were just more respectful and polite?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, yes, but I'm socked about what you're saying because it's humorous for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "You could not get in the room.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "So you just wonder, where are we going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Yes, I think it's a shame.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Isn't he awesome?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Yes, he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Did you enjoy that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 502, "question": "If I was to pin you down and say, right, what has been the greatest moment of your life, what would you say it's been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "When it comes to entertainment or just --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "``", "RB", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Yes, \"Fly Me to the Moon.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "-- you retire?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tony Bennett"]}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Danny, what do you think's been the secret of your father's success, if you were to try and crystallize it, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I mean, I think, you know, again, it's -- I'm doing a documentary called \"The Zen of Tony Bennett,\" and it is that focus.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "You work out every day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Is it -- is it just because you do something you love, just working as hard as you can to keep the passion burning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I believe that's absolutely correct, the way -- what you described is the way I feel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]